Guide to the Rights and Wrongs Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Camera Originals, Circa 1990-1996; Series I
  - RT94 1079, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1079)
  - RT94 1080, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1080)
  - RT94 1081, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1081)
  - RT94 1082, Undated (Box RT94_1082)
  - RT94 1083, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1083)
  - RT94 1084, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1084)
  - RT94 1085, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1085)
  - RT94 1086, 1994 March 16 (Box RT94_1086)
  - RT94 1087, 1994 March 16 (Box RT94_1087)
  - RT94 1088, 1994 March 16 (Box RT94_1088)
  - RT94 1089, 1994 March 17 (Box RT94_1089)
  - RT94 1090, 1994 March 17 (Box RT94_1090)
  - RT94 1091, 1994 March 18 (Box RT94_1091)
  - RT94 1092, 1994 March 18 (Box RT94_1092)
  - RT94 1093, Undated (Box RT94_1093)
  - RT94 1094, 1994 March 19 (Box RT94_1094)
  - RT94 1095, 1994 March 19 (Box RT94_1095)
  - RT94 1096, 1994 March 20 (Box RT94_1096)
  - RT94 1097, 1994 March 20 (Box RT94_1097)
  - RT94 1098, 1994 March 20 (Box RT94_1098)
  - RT94 1099, 1994 March 21 (Box RT94_1099)
  - RT94 1100, 1994 March 21 (Box RT94_1100)
  - RT94 1101, 1994 March 24 (Box RT94_1101)
  - RT94 1102, 1994 March 24 (Box RT94_1102)
  - RT94 1105, 1994 March 28 (Box RT94_1105)
  - RT94 1106, 1994 March 28 (Box RT94_1106)
  - RT94 1107, 1994 March 29 (Box RT94_1107)
  - RT94 1108, 1994 March 29 (Box RT94_1108)
  - RT94 1109, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1109)
  - RT94 1110, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1110)
  - RT94 1111, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1111)
  - RT94 1117, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1117)
  - RT94 1118, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1118)
  - RT94 1119, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1119)
  - RT94 1120, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1120)
  - RT94 1121, 1994 March 30 (Box RT94_1121)
  - RT94 1122, Undated (Box RT94_1122)
  - RT94 1123, Undated (Box RT94_1123)
  - RT94 1124, Undated (Box RT94_1124)
  - RT94 1125, 1994 April 5 (Box RT94_1125)
  - RT94 1126, 1994 April 5 (Box RT94_1126)
  - RT94 1129, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1129)
  - RT94 1130, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1130)
  - RT94 1131, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1131)
  - RT94 1132, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1132)
  - RT94 1133, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1133)
  - RT94 1134, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1134)
  - RT94 1135, 1994 April 7 (Box RT94_1135)
  - RT94 1136, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1136)
  - RT94 1137, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1137)
  - RT94 1138, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1138)
  - RT94 1139, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1139)
  - RT94 1140, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1140)
  - RT94 1141, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1141)
  - RT94 1142, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1142)
  - RT94 1143, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1143)
  - RT94 1144, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1144)
  - RT94 1145, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1145)
  - RT94 1151, 1994 April 12 (Box RT94_1151)
  - RT94 1152, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1152)
  - RT94 1153, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1153)
  - RT94 1154, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1154)
  - RT94 1155, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1155)
  - RT94 1156, 1994 April 13 (Box RT94_1156)
  - RT94 1157, 1994 March 9 (Box RT94_1157)
  - RT94 1158, 1994 April 14 (Box RT94_1158)
  - RT94 1159, 1994 April 15 (Box RT94_1159)
  - RT94 1160, 1994 April 15 (Box RT94_1160)
  - RT94 1161, 1994 April 14 (Box RT94_1161)
  - RT94 1162, 1994 April 14 (Box RT94_1162)
  - RT94 1163, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1166, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1167, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1168, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1169, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1171, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1172, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1173, 1994 April 16 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1174, Undated (Box 26)
  - RT94 1175, 1994 April 15 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1176, 1994 April 15 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1177, 1994 April 20 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1178, 1994 April 20 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1179, 1994 April 20 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1180, 1994 April 20 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1181, 1994 March 10 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1182, 1994 March 24 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1183, 1994 April 15 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1184, 1994 April 15 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1185, 1994 April 15 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1186, 1994 April 21 (Box 26)
  - RT94 1187, 1994 April 21 (Box 26)
  - RT941188, 1994 April 20 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1189, 1994 April 21 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1190, 1994 April 20 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1191, 1994 April 21 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1192, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1193, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1194, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1195, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1196, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1197, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1198, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1199, 1994 April 22 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1200, 1994 April 19 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1201, 1994 April 23 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1202, 1994 April 23 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1205, 1994 April 27 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1206, 1994 May 1 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1207, 1994 May 1 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1208, 1994 May 1 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1209, 1994 May 1 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1210, 1994 May 1 (Box 27)
  - RT94 1211, 1994 May 2 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1212, 1994 May 1 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1213, 1994 May 1 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1214, 1994 April 1 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1215, 1994 May 2 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1216, 1994 May 2 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1217, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
    Interview with Rigoberta Menchu at the Embassy Suites. She names the foundations she has established. [Tape 1 of 2]. Beta done for episode 411.
  - RT94 1217, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
    Interview with Rigoberta Menchu at the Embassy Suites. She names the foundations she has established. [Tape 1 of 2]. VHS done for episode 411.
  - RT94 1218, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
    Interview with Rigoberta Menchu at the Embassy Suites. [Tape 2 of 2]. Beta done for episode 411.
  - RT94 1219, Undated (Box 28)
  - RT94 1220, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1221, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1222, 1994 May 5 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1223, 1994 April 27 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1224, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1225, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1226, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1227, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1228, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1229, 1994 May 6 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1230, 1994 May 9 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1232, Undated (Box 28)
  - RT94 1233, 1994 May 10 (Box 28)
  - RT94 1234, 1994 May 10 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1235, 1994 May 11 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1236, 1993 June 23 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1237, 1994 May 18 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1238, 1994 May 16 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1239, 1994 May 16 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1242, Undated (Box 29)
  - RT94 1243, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1244, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1245, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1246, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1247, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1248, Undated (Box 29)
  - RT94 1249, Undated (Box 29)
  - RT94 1250, 1994 May 23 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1251, 1994 May 23 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1252, 1994 May 25 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1253, 1994 May 20 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1254, 1994 May 19 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1255, 1994 May 19 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1256, 1994 May 22 (Box 29)
  - RT94 1257, 1994 May 31 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1258, 1994 May 30 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1259, 1994 June 1 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1260, 1994 May 1 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1261, 1994 May 1 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1262, 1994 May 31 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1263, Undated (Box 30)
  - RT94 1264, 1994 June 3 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1265, 1994 June 3 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1266, 1994 June 3 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1267, 1994 June 6 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1268, 1994 June 7 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1269, 1994 June 7 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1270, 1994 June 7 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1271, 1994 June 7 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1272, 1994 June 8 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1273, 1994 June 8 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1274, 1994 June 9 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1275, 1994 June 8 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1276, 1994 June 8 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1277, 1994 June 8 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1278, 1994 June 9 (Box 30)
  - RT94 1286, 1994 June 23 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1279, 1994 June 9 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1280, 1994 June 20 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1281, 1994 June 20 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1282, 1994 June 24 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1287, 1994 June 23 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1288, 1994 June 23 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1289, 1994 June 23 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1290, 1994 June 25 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1291, 1994 April 28 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1292, 1994 August 11 (Box 31)
  - RT94 1293, 1994 August 11 (Box 31)
  - RT95 0001, Undated (Box 31)
  - RT95 0002, Undated (Box 31)
  - RT95 0003, Undated (Box 31)
  - RT95 1001, 1994 November 16 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1005, 1994 December 1 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1006, 1994 December 21 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1007, 1994 December 6 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1008, 1994 December 6 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1009, 1994 December 6 (Box 31)
  - RT95 1010, 1994 December 6 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1011, 1994 December 6 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1012, 1994 December 7 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1013, 1994 December 7 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1014, Undated (Box 32)
  - RT95 1016, 1995 January 26 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1017, 1995 February 8 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1018, 1995 February 14 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1019, 1995 February 14 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1020, 1995 February 14 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1022, 1995 January 24 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1024, 1995 February 25 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1025, 1995 February 25 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1026, 1995 February 25 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1027, 1995 February 25 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1028, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1029, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1030, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1031, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1032, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1033, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1034, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1035, 1995 February 1 (Box 32)
  - RT95 1036, 1995 February 1 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1037, 1995 February 1 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1039, 1995 March 9 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1040, Undated (Box 33)
  - RT95 1041, 1995 March 9 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1042, 1995 March 9 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1043, 1995 March 9 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1044, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1045, Undated (Box 33)
  - RT95 1046, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1047, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1048, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1049, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1050, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1051, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1052, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1053, 1995 March 10 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1055, Undated (Box 33)
  - RT95 1056, 1994 October 17 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1057, 1994 October 17 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1058, 1994 October 17 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1061, 1995 March 16 (Box 33)
  - RT95 1062, 1995 March 17 (Box 33)
    Interview with Geoffrey Canada and friends about life growing up in the South Bronx. Beta Done for Episode 411.
  - RT95 1062, 1995 March 17 (Box 33)
    Interview with Geoffrey Canada and friends about life growing up in the South Bronx. VHS Done for Episode 411.
  - RT95 1063, 1995 March 17 (Box 33)
    Interview with Geoffrey Canada about life growing up in the South Bronx, and footage of South Bronx stores and housing. Beta Done for Episode 411.
  - RT95 1063, 1995 March 17 (Box 33)
    Interview with Geoffrey Canada about life growing up in the South Bronx, and footage of South Bronx stores and housing. VHS Done for Episode 411.
  - RT95 1065, 1995 March 17 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1066, 1995 March 20 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1067, 1995 March 20 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1068, 1995 March 14 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1069, 1995 March 14 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1070, 1995 March 14 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1071, 1995 March 13 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1072, 1995 March 13 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1076, 1995 March 23 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1078, Undated (Box 34)
  - RT95 1079, 1995 March 30 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1080, 1995 April 3 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1081, 1995 April 3 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1082, 1995 March 28 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1083, 1995 March 28 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1084, 1995 March 28 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1085, 1995 March 29 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1086, 1995 March 29 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1087, 1995 March 29 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1088, 1995 March 29 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1089, 1995 March 29 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1090, 1995 April 4 (Box 34)
  - RT95 1091, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1092, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1093, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1094, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1095, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1096, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1097, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1098, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1099, 1995 April 4 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1100, 1995 March 19 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1101, 1995 April 6 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1102, 1995 April 6 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1103, 1995 April 6 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1104, 1995 April 6 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1105, 1995 April 6 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1106, 1995 April 12 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1107, 1995 April 12 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1108, Undated (Box 35)
  - RT95 1109, Undated (Box 35)
  - RT95 1110, 1995 April 17 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1110, Undated (Box 35)
  - RT95 1111, 1995 April 17 (Box 35)
  - RT95 1112, Undated (Box 35)
  - RT95 1113, Undated (Box 36)
  - RT95 1114, 1995 April 19 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1115, 1995 April 19 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1116, 1995 April 19 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1119, 1995 April 20 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1120B, 1995 April 20 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1120A, 1995 April 20 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1121A, Undated (Box 36)
  - RT95 1122, 1995 April 26 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1123, 1995 April 26 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1124, 1995 April 26 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1125, 1995 April 28 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1126, 1995 April 28 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1126A, Undated (Box 36)
  - RT95 1127, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1128, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1129, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1130, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1131, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1132, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1133, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1134, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1135, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1136, 1995 May 1 (Box 36)
  - RT95 1137, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1138, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1139, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1140, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1141, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1142, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1143, 1995 May 2 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1144, 1995 May 4 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1146, 1995 May 8 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1147, 1995 May 8 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1148, 1995 May 8 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1149, 1995 May 8 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1150, 1995 May 8 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1151, 1995 May 10 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1152, 1995 May 10 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1153, 1995 May 10 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1154, 1995 May 10 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1155, Undated (Box 37)
  - RT95 1156, 1995 May 4 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1157, 1995 May 4 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1158, 1995 May 12 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1159, 1995 May 16 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1160, 1995 May 16 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1161, 1995 May 17 (Box 37)
  - RT95 1162, 1995 May 17 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1164, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1165, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1166, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1167, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1168, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1169, 1995 May 3 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1170, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1172, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1173, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1174, Undated (Box 38)
  - RT95 1175, 1995 May 21 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1176, 1995 May 21 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1177, 1995 May 21 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1178, 1995 May 21 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1179, 1995 May 21 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1180, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1181, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1181, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1183, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1184, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1185, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1186, 1995 May 22 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1187, 1995 May 23 (Box 38)
  - RT95 1188, 1995 May 23 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1189, 1995 May 23 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1190, 1995 May 23 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1191, 1995 May 23 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1192, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1193, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1194, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1195, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1196, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1197, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1198, 1995 May 24 (Box 39)
  - RT95 1201, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1202, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1203, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1204, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1205, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1206, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1207, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1208, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1209, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1210, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1211, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1212, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1213, Undated (Box 39)
  - RT95 1214, 1995 May 30 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1215, 1995 May 30 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1216, 1995 May 30 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1217, 1995 May 30 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1218, 1995 May 30 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1219, 1995 May 31 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1220, 1995 May 31 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1221, 1995 May 31 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1222, 1995 May 31 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1223, 1995 May 31 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1226, 1995 June 23 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1227, 1995 June 23 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1228, 1995 June 23 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1229, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1230, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1231, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1232, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1250, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1251, Undated (Box 40)
  - RT95 1252, 1995 May 11 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1253, 1995 May 11 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1254, 1995 May 11 (Box 40)
  - RT95 1255, 1995 May 11 (Box 40)
  - RT96 1005, 1996 February 6 (Box 41)
  - RT96 1006, 1996 February 6 (Box 41)
  - RT96 1008, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1009, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1010, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1440, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1440, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1441, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1441, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1442, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1442, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1443, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1444, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1445, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1445, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1446, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1446, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1447, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1448, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1449, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1450, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1451, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1452, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1453, Undated (Box 41)
  - RT96 1015, 1996 March 7 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1016, 1996 March 7 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1017, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1018, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1019, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1020, 1996 March 18 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1021, 1996 March 18 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1022, 1996 March 18 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1023, 1996 March 18 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1024, 1996 March 18 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1025, 1996 March 22 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1026, 1996 March 22 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1027, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1028, 1996 March 26 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1029, 1996 March 26 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1030, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1031, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1032, Undated (Box 42)
  - RT96 1033, 1996 April 2 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1035, 1996 April 2 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1036, 1996 April 10 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1037, 1996 April 10 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1038, 1996 April 10 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1039, 1996 April 10 (Box 42)
  - RT96 1040, 1996 October 4 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1041, 1996 April 12 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1042, 1996 April 12 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1043, 1996 April 23 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1044, 1996 April 23 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1045, 1996 April 23 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1046, 1996 February 4 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1047, 1996 February 4 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1048, 1996 February 4 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1049, 1996 July 4 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1050, 1996 April 26 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1051, 1996 April 26 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1052, 1996 April 26 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1053, 1996 April 30 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1054, 1996 April 29 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1055, 1996 April 30 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1056, 1996 April 26 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1057, 1996 April 30 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1058, 1996 April 29 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1059, 1996 May 2 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1060, 1996 May 2 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1061, 1996 April 30 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1062, 1996 April 30 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1063, 1996 April 14 (Box 43)
  - RT96 1064, 1996 May 6 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1065, 1996 May 6 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1066, 1996 May 6 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1067, 1996 March 27 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1068, 1996 April 3 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1069, 1996 May 8 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1070, 1996 May 8 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1071, 1996 April 26 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1072, 1996 April 24 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1073, 1996 April 24 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1075, 1996 May 21 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1076, 1996 May 21 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1077, 1996 May 21 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1078, 1996 May 21 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1079, 1996 May 21 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1080, 1996 April 23 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1081, 1996 May 23 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1082, Undated (Box 44)
  - RT96 1083, 1996 May 9 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1084, 1996 May 6 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1085, 1996 May 7 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1086, 1996 May 9 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1087, 1996 June 1 (Box 44)
  - RT96 1088, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1089, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1090, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1091, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1092, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1093, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1094, 1996 June 1 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1095, 1996 June 6 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1096, 1996 June 6 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1097, 1996 June 6 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1098, 1996 June 6 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1001, Undated (Box 45)
  - RT96 1002, Undated (Box 45)
  - RT96 1003, Undated (Box 45)
  - RT96 1004, Undated (Box 45)
  - RT96 1102, 1996 May 10 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1103, 1996 May 10 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1104, 1996 March 27 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1106, 1996 June 17 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1107, 1996 June 12 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1108, 1996 June 12 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1110, 1996 June 19 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1111, 1996 June 18 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1115, 1996 June 21 (Box 45)
  - RT96 1114, 1996 June 18 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1116, 1996 June 18 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1117, 1996 June 21 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1118, 1996 June 28 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1119, 1996 June 28 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1120, 1996 June 28 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1121, 1996 June 28 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1122, 1996 June 26 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1123, 1996 June 26 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1124, 1996 June 26 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1125, 1996 July 2 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1126, 1996 July 1 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1127, 1996 July 1 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1128, 1996 July 1 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1129, 1996 July 1 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1130, 1996 July 1 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1132, 1996 July 2 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1133, 1996 July 10 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1134, 1996 July 10 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1135, 1996 July 10 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1136, 1996 July 11 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1137, 1996 July 11 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1138, 1996 July 11 (Box 46)
  - RT96 1139, 1996 July 11 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1140, 1996 July 12 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1141, 1996 June 13 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1142, 1996 January 16 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1143, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1144, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1145, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1146, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1147, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1148, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1149, 1996 June 27 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1150, 1996 July 9 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1151, 1996 July 2 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1152, 1996 July 15 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1153, 1996 July 15 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1154, 1996 July 15 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1155, 1996 July 15 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1156, 1996 July 15 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1157, 1996 July 16 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1158, 1996 July 16 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1159, 1996 July 16 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1160, 1996 July 16 (Box 47)
  - RT96 1161, 1996 July 16 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1162, 1996 July 16 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1163, 1996 July 24 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1164, 1996 July 22 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1165, 1995 November 13 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1166, 1996 January 16 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1167, 1996 July 15 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1168, 1996 July 16 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1169, 1996 July 16 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1170, 1996 June 1 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1171, 1996 June 1 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1172, Undated (Box 48)
  - RT96 1173, Undated (Box 48)
  - RT96 1175, Undated (Box 48)
  - RT96 1176, 1996 September 24 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1177, 1996 September 24 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1178, 1996 September 26 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1179, 1996 September 26 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1180, 1996 September 26 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1181, 1996 September 26 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1182, 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1183, 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1184, 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1185, 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1186, 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
  - RT96 1187, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1188, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1189, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1190, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1191, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1191, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1192, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1192, 1996 May 30 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1193, 1996 October 16 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1193, 1996 October 16 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1194, 1996 October 16 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1195, 1996 October 16 (Box 49)
  - RT96 1198, Undated (Box 49)
  - RT96 1199, Undated (Box 49)